bestqualityplr.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Best Quality PLR

Best Quality PLR is dedicated to preserving your privacy, this page will explain what information we do collect, and how we use it.

**Types and Uses of Personal Information**

Your personal information is used in the following ways:  
**  
****User IDs and Passwords** : Provide you with access to the members areas and to protected content.

**IP Address** : An IP address is recorded at the time of order placement. This is used only for the purposes of fraud prevention.

**Account Information** : Tells us more about who you are, how to contact you, and your billing information. Also contains any preferences you have provided, such as e-mail format and interests.

**Customer Feedback and Support** : Provides a mechanism for requesting information from our support portal. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site design.

**E-mail Correspondence** : Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information, email newsletters about our products, and services.

**Transactions** : Show which products and services you have requested.

We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.

**Security Measures**

We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job.

We may collect and possibly share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations o Best Quality PLR’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Data Retention**

BestQualityPLR will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Linked Web Sites**

We provide links to third-party sites. Since we do not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third-party sites. Best Quality PLR is not responsible for third party content.

**Cookies**

The Best Quality PLR website may occasionally use cookies. Cookies help us provide a better user experience by measuring which web pages are of greatest interest. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access the members only area of the website.

Current versions of web browsers offer enhanced user controls regarding the placement and duration of both first and third party cookies. Search for “cookies” under your Web browser’s help menu for more information on cookie management features available to you.

**Newsletters**

Each e-mail newsletter has instructions on how to unsubscribe.

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using the Best Quality PLR site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Best Quality PLR as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Whom do I contact if I have additional questions or concerns about this policy?**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please [contact us.](http://bestqualityplr.com/contact/)

Note: This policy may be modified from time to time. You are encouraged to review this policy each time you visit this site.

_Dated: April, 19 2013_
